Hear, hear.
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)That was perfect.
(Howard:)What? You gotta be kidding me?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, we've been
together so long,
(Leonard:)it's hard to remember a time
you weren't in my life.
(Leonard:)And believe me, I try.
(laughter)
(Leonard:)You make me laugh.
(Leonard:)You make me a better scientist.
(Leonard:)You make me crazy.
(Leonard:)You're more than just
my roommate,
(Leonard:)you're my brother.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)Happy birthday, buddy.
ALL:
Cheers.
(Penny:)Thank you.
That-that was wonderful.
PENNY:
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
(Penny:)Stuart didn't get to speak.
(Stuart:)Oh, oh, okay. Um...
(Howard:)Uh, Sheldon,
(Stuart:)I've spent most of my life
feeling invisible,
(Stuart:)but having you and everyone...
(Amy:)Hey, everybody, listen up.
(Penny:)You nailed it.
(Amy:)We've got someone
who couldn't be here
(Amy:)but really wanted to wish you
(Amy:)a happy birthday.
(Stephen Hawking(on Skype):)Hello, Sheldon.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)Professor Hawking.
(chuckles)